timetastic.co.uk 2016-04-16

# Privacy Policy - Timetastic

## Privacy Policy

We believe your private information should be just that, private. Clearly, to operate our services we need to collect some personal information about you. This policy explains what we do and why we do it.

## What we collect

We ask for your name and email address when you signup to our service. This is our primary mechanism to identify you.

## How we store the information

We take great care to keep your personal information safe, all our live services and databases operate from computers that are housed in secure data centres with heavily restricted access. We operate numerous levels of security to prevent unauthorised access to those computers including firewalls and passwords.

## What we do with the information

Email is a vital part of Timetastic, emails are used to communicate time off requests and confirmations to users. We don’t allow users to opt out of these emails. We also use email to send occasional alerts, reminders and newsletters in relation to Timetastic and how you use Timetastic, all these emails contain a link that allows a user to opt out of further communication with a single click.

## Who we share the information with

To help us deliver Timetastic we use various 3rd party apps:

Google Analytics collects statistical data about your use of our website and application. We use the information to understand the way people use Timetastic so we can make it better and communicate relevant information to users. We believe Google is reputable and takes appropriate steps to ensure your data remains safe.

We also use Campaign Monitor for sending broadcast emails and Zendesk for customer services. Both are reputable market leading companies and do not use your personal data for anything other than helping us deliver Timetastic to you. Both publish their Privacy Policies.

## What we don’t and won’t ever do

We don’t, and never will sell or rent your private information to any 3rd party.

## Updates to this policy

We update this privacy policy from time-to-time, particularly as technology changes and as Timetastic develops. We suggest you check back from time to time for the latest version.

## Any questions?

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or your personal data, please send us an email to [hello@timetastic.co.uk](mailto:hello@timetastic.co.uk).
